worldofmoms.com 2008-03-27

# World of Moms

**Updated July 2005**

At ‘ **World of Moms** ’®, we are committed to maintaining your privacy and trust. This privacy policy explains how we collect, protect, use, and share information about you, including on our Web site, and/or through your membership in ‘ **World of Moms** ’. We hope this information increases your confidence in ‘ **World of Moms** ’ and enhances your experience on our Web site. Please see our separate ‘ **World of Moms** ’ Terms and Conditions which serves as the membership agreement between ‘ **World of Moms** ’ and our members.

**Information We Collect**

**Traffic Data.** We collect the following information from you automatically when you visit our site: 

* The name of the domain through which you access the Internet

* The date and time you access our site; 

* The Internet address from which you linked to our site (the Web page you "clicked" from to get to our Web site);

* The unique Internet address of the computer you used to access our site;   
Your browser (i.e., Internet Explorer 5.5); and

* The operating system of your computer (i.e., Microsoft Windows NT 4.0).

We use this information to administer and improve your experience on our Web site, to help diagnose and troubleshoot potential server malfunctions, and to gather broad demographic information.

**Personal Information** **We Collect.** You do not have to be a ‘ **World of Moms** ’ member to visit our Web site and access much of our content and tools. However, as a non-member visitor, you may not have access to some of the most popular features that ‘ **World of Moms** ’.com offers. For example, only members can post on our ‘Community’ section, use the ‘ **World of Moms** Special Solutions’ and Deals section. 

In order to register to become a ‘ **World of Moms** ’ member, you need to provide us with the following information: 

* Your name; 

* Your address; 

* Your email address(if you register online);

* Your place of birth; and 

* Your postal code. 

We may also ask you certain questions related to your purchasing preferences.   
We will also ask you for your phone number, no of children and other information, but you will still be included as a member if some of this information is not provided to us.

We may collect information about you through other methods, including research surveys or information we obtain from third parties, including verification services, data services, as well as public sources. We use this information to continually offer you the most value as a ‘ **World of Moms** ’ member. 

Use of Cookies and Other Technologies. To help make sure you receive information that is relevant to you, our site uses data "cookies." These cookies are small data files stored on your computer which identify you as a previous visitor to the site and help us to personalize your experience when you arrive. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. You can instruct your browser not to accept cookies. However, if you disable this function, you will not be able to use some of the features on our site. 

Our Web pages and our e-mail newsletters contain "web beacons". Web beacons allow us to count users that have visited a web page or opened an email that contains a web beacon. Using this information, we are able to measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. This allows us to learn what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which parts of our site are the most interesting and what kind of offers our members like to see. Some of the web beacons that are in place on our site are used only by ‘ **World of Moms** ’, and other web beacons are from our vendors and advertisers who use this data to assist us in analyzing how our members use the site. In addition, we have agreements with various affiliate networks that promote ‘ **World of Moms** ’ on their affiliate web sites. These affiliate advertisers may use web beacons in their advertisements to track users who click through from the affiliate web site to the ‘ **World of Moms** ’ web site. 

**Uses of Information**  
At ‘ **World of Moms** ’, everything we do, including how we handle your personal information, is designed to show how much we value moms. Your information assists us in understanding the kinds of benefits and services that may suit your needs and interests. Other than as described herein, we do not share your personal information with any third parties outside of our existing and potential partners. 

‘ **World of Moms’ partners with a number of companies** , which are listed on our Web site and our emails. We may share individually identifying information about you with these partners so that they can augment their customer files, execute the ‘ **World of Moms** ’ Program and measure its success, deliver products or services that you have requested, or perform market research. However, our partners will only use your individually identifying information to send direct solicitations if you agree to receive them, or if you are an existing customer or become a customer of these companies. On occasion, we will share information about our members with potential partners, but this information will only be used in an aggregated form or limited to research purposes to determine the feasibility of a future partnership arrangement. 

**Agents and Services Providers**. Sometime we hire third parties to provide services that we need to operate our business such as to send email, analyze and update data, ‘ **World of Moms** special solutions’, provide marketing services, process applications and other functions. In those instances, we need to share your personal information with those companies. These companies are allowed to use your information only for purposes of performing the function that we have hired them to perform. 

**We may share your information with your referring ‘World of Moms’ Ambassador**. If you were referred to ‘ **World of Moms** ’ by a ‘ **World of Moms** ’ Ambassador, you probably included her member number or other identifying information on the registration form that you completed when you joined. We will inform that Ambassador that you joined ‘ **World of Moms** ’ and we may share some of your individually identifiable information with her. 

**We may send regular newsletters and other correspondence to our members.** After you register for ‘ **World of Moms** ’, you may receive communications from us including those in which we may describe specific offers from our partners, as well as news and updates related to ‘ **World of Moms** ’. You may opt out of receiving ‘ **World of Moms** ’ correspondence (i) at any time simply by updating your account, which you can do by clicking on the "Edit Profile" button posted throughout the site, or (ii) by opting-out of receiving future emails as described at the bottom of each communication from ‘ **World of Moms** ’. 

**We use demographic** data collected at our site to personalize your visit. With this data, we can provide content applicable to your particular location and interests. General, non-identifying information regarding the total number of visitors to our site and the services the visitors used will be shared with sponsors, advertisers, and partners who offer services relevant to our members. 

**On occasion, we offer promotions** -like sweepstakes or free subscriptions or special products or service offers-in conjunction with a sponsor. By participating in a promotion, you submit to that promotion's terms and conditions including providing us with permission, if required, to share your information with a particular sponsor. 

**Third Party Offers**. On occasion, we are able to offer you special products or services through a relationship with a third party. In those cases, the offer will be brought to you by ‘ **World of Moms** ’ and fulfilled by the third party. If you accept the offer, you will become a customer of the company that is fulfilling the offer and we will not have control over their use of the information that you provide to them when you accept the offer. 

‘ **World of Moms’ also has bulletin boards in ‘Community’ section where members may post messages on various topics.** Any messages you post on these boards will become public, and any personal information you post will be accessible to anyone who visits that message board. In addition, your member name or first name with first initial of last name, and city/state will be shown with the posting. Please see ‘ **World of Moms** ’'s Terms and Conditions for rules related to posting messages on the ‘ **World of Moms** ’ Web site. 

**Refer a Friend**

If you do become a member, not only can you enjoy all of the benefits of membership, but you can also refer other individuals to join by providing us with their first names and email addresses. Using the information you give us on these potential members, we will send them an email invitation to join ‘ **World of Moms** ’. The only way these individuals can become members, however, is if they come to our site and sign up themselves. We do not use this information for any other purposes. 

‘ **World of Moms’.com contains** links to other sites. It is possible for you to receive information directly from our partners and other companies if you access them through a link on ‘ **World of Moms** ’.com or if you go directly to their Web sites. Once you are on their sites, any data that you supply to these partners, for example, to obtain information or buy products directly from them is beyond our reach and will be the responsibility of each of the linked-to entities and not ‘ **World of Moms** ’. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these Web sites or any other sites linked to or referenced on our site. 

**We may receive requests to transfer information for legal purposes.** We will disclose the identities of our users to comply with law or a legal request, such as a subpoena, court order, or other legal proceeding. We may also disclose personal information in order to enforce our rights under our agreement with our members or to protect the rights, property and safety of our members, employees and partners, including exchanging information for fraud and theft protection. 

**Sale of Business or Assets.** In the event that ‘ **World of Moms** ’, substantially all of its assets, or a line of business are acquired, individually identifying information of our members may be one of the assets sold in connection with that transaction. ‘ **World of Moms** ’ will notify users of the Web site of such a change in ownership or transfer of assets by posting a notice on the Web site. 

**Security**

‘ **World of Moms** ’ has multiple layers of security on its systems. We have implemented software and hardware security, including firewalls, data encryption, and private networks to protect your information from unauthorized access. 

We protect our network with Cisco Systems firewalls and intrusion-detection devices that defend against hackers and are designed to notify us if any attempts are made to compromise our network. 

Our Web site utilizes SSL encryption when transmitting sensitive data such as credit card information. 

Finally, we constantly review additional software upgrades to enhance our security measures. 

**Children's Privacy**

None of ‘ **World of Moms** ’'s products or services are intended for purchase by children. Further, members must be 18 years old or older to join ‘ **World of Moms** ’. Accordingly, ‘ **World of Moms** ’ does not knowingly, either offline or online, collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. 

**Updating Your Personal Information** If you are a ‘ **World of Moms** ’ member, you can update your information at any time by accessing your Account. To do this, just click on the "My Account" link listed throughout the site. 

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
We will inform you if we substantially modify the way we handle your personally identifiable information by posting a notice on the Web site, and we will give you the opportunity to opt-out of whether we use your information in a different manner than described above. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on the ‘ **World of Moms** ’ Web site. 

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, or the practices of this Web site, please contact: privacy@worldofmoms.com
